<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="9D03D445-7FEC-4DBE-86B0-788FB2F70D22">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20111126" date="2011-11-26 13:03:12 -0800"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Trussworks Blog&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Trussworks news! New people, new website!</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Dear Trussworks Distributor,&#xD;&#xD;First off, I want to thank all of you for your business. We have had some phenomenal success over the past couple of years since the introduction of our EZ truss systems and we know it is all due to you guys, our distributors.&#xA0;&#xD;&#xD;Secondly, we have some exciting news as far as our distributor support.&#xA0;&#xD;&#xD;First, customer service news.&#xA0;&#xD;Last year, Chris Morita re-joined our team after 9 years with us and then striking out on his own in 2001. He left again at the end of the year to manage a La-Z-Boy store but he really missed the industry and the atmosphere at Trussworks. He is a wealth of knowledge, ability and good will and we are so happy to have him back. He can be reached via email at &lt;a href="mailto:chris@trussworks.com"&gt;chris@trussworks.com&lt;/a&gt; or phone 800-598-9738 ext. 105.&#xA0;&#xD;&#xD;His smart and talented teammate, Jerami Surratt, a staff sergeant in the Marine reserves, is currently off serving our country again, this time in Thailand. He'll be back on June 11th and once again available at &lt;a href="mailto:jerami@trussworks.com"&gt;jerami@trussworks.com&lt;/a&gt; or phone 800-598-9738 ext. 107.&#xA0;&#xD;&#xD;Together these two make up the most talented customer service team Trussworks has ever had and they are here for you. Please feel free to use and abuse them as you feel necessary.&#xD;&#xD;Next, product info online.&#xA0;&#xD;The Trussworks site has been stagnant and outdated for 7 years. Just before Exhibitor, we started overhauling the site. We started with EZ6 and have been working our way through the product lines. The site is organized by product line, traditional truss, EZ6. Pack Stuff furniture and EZ12 collapsible truss. Basically, we are trying to answer the questions most asked to save you time.&#xD;&#xD;Some of the highlights are as follows..&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;EZ6&lt;/b&gt; is the most complete and here is a quick breakdown of the sections.&#xA0;&lt;a href="http://www.trussworks.com/EZ6_Main_Product_Page.html"&gt;http://www.trussworks.com/EZ6_Main_Product_Page.html&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xD;Kits - A start page that links to the various size kits for EZ6. &#xA0;Within each section are a number of predesigned and priced out kits. The prices are retail. Click on a kit image to learn more about the kit. This brings you to a page that includes the large image, available accessories, a plan view, a graphic panel guide and a link to an exploded view of the booth!&#xA0;&#xD;Here is a link to a sample kit page..&#xA0;&lt;a href="http://www.trussworks.com/EZ6_Bayview.html"&gt;http://www.trussworks.com/EZ6_Bayview.html&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;From the main kit page, you can also access counters walls and accessories.&#xA0;&lt;a href="http://www.trussworks.com/EZ6_Counters.html"&gt;http://www.trussworks.com/EZ6_Counters.html&lt;/a&gt;&#xA0;While this is not a complete list of accessories, if you scroll down near the bottom, you will find some new treats.. We now have a vertical mount articulating arm flat screen mount and a cable mounted 8 pocket literature holder. From this page, you can also access our fabric color options. These are used for our counter bases as well as wall panels.&#xA0;&lt;a href="http://www.trussworks.com/Color_options.html"&gt;http://www.trussworks.com/Color_options.html&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xD;Parts - this is the basic 4 page section of the catalog showing the components that make up the system.&#xD;&#xD;Instructions - this is a page with links to each pdf we have illustrating how to set up a cabinet, how to install a fabric graphic, assemble a corner bracket, etc. It also has a link to each exploded view kit pdf.&#xD;&#xD;Photo Gallery - speaks for itself, due to our rental business and the graciousness of our customers, we have assembled a substantial amount of photographs of our products actually on the show floor. check it out to get even more ideas of how to use EZ6!&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;EZ12&lt;/b&gt; is set up much the same way.&#xA0;&lt;a href="http://www.trussworks.com/EZ12_Main_Product_Page.html"&gt;http://www.trussworks.com/EZ12_Main_Product_Page.html&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;There are some very nice new kits in our kit section and the instructions page actually contains a You-Tube video of how to use each bracket.&#xA0;&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Traditional Truss&lt;/b&gt;&#xA0;is also like that but we have not gotten too far into kit support yet. That will be coming in the next month or two.&#xA0;&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Pack Stuff&lt;/b&gt; is just our furniture catalog with a link to the pricing.&#xD;&#xD;Anyway, we hope this helps and we hope you keep checking back as we continue to develop products and add kits to our libraries. This is a very exciting time for Trussworks and we look forward to any input you may have as to products, accessories, or distributor support.&#xD;&#xD;Thanks for reading!&#xD;&#xD;Roy&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Monday, May 12, 2008&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
