<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog</title>
    <link>http://www.trussworks.com/trussworks/Blog</link>
    <description>Trying to make sure everyone gets our updates has turned into a challenge so in addition to the email updates we send out periodically, whenever we have something useful to say, we will post it here, our little blog corner. If you are one of those that doesn&#x2019;t save and organize emails, it&#x2019;s okay, just check back here.. often!

Thank you for reading!</description>
    <item>
      <title>Trussworks booth #969</title>
      <link>http://www.trussworks.com/trussworks/Blog/Entries/2015/11/17_Trussworks_booth_969.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b210ef9f-2f40-48c1-ae25-0720c48dacd5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 09:56:21 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>At Exhibitor LIVE 2016, we are doing something new, different, and exciting. We have teamed up with SoftSpace, combining our 30&#x2019; x 25&#x2019; spaces to make a 30 x 50 space where we will showcase our complimentary skillsets in building one beautiful exhibit bringing life to the words &#x201C;Let&#x2019;s Build Something Together..&#x201D; It&#x2019;s not only an invitation to you to participate but a demonstration of how it can be done.. We look forward to seeing you in Vegas!</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object001.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment link="http://www.trussworks.com/trussworks/Blog/Entries/2015/11/17_Trussworks_booth_969.html#comment_layer" count="0" enabled="0"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See us at Booth #1257</title>
      <link>http://www.trussworks.com/trussworks/Blog/Entries/2013/1/25_See_us_at_Booth_1257.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78e6a326-76f5-402d-8d99-a2b9f47e5cc7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 11:58:41 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>Another Exhibitor is fast approaching. &lt;a href="https://www.compusystems.com/servlet/ar?evt_uid=136&amp;company_code=4237"&gt;Click here to be our guest to the exhibit hall and reception at Exhibitor 2013. &lt;/a&gt;Exhibitor is the place to see all of the industry&#x2019;s best and learn about what&#x2019;s new. If you haven&#x2019;t been lately, come see us in Vegas!</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object002.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment link="http://www.trussworks.com/trussworks/Blog/Entries/2013/1/25_See_us_at_Booth_1257.html#comment_layer" count="0" enabled="0"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trussworks Double Deck a hit at Exhibitor &#x2019;12</title>
      <link>http://www.trussworks.com/trussworks/Blog/Entries/2012/5/26_Trussworks_Double_Deck_a_hit_at_Exhibitor_12.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">acd54534-4286-46b4-9866-3eb63d15b401</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 18:35:02 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>We introduced our new double deck system at Exhibitor in Las Vegas in March. It was an absolute hit. Attendees raved about the clean lines, integrated ceiling and lighting and the ease of installing graphics and other accessories. Our deck system goes beyond just structural. It is beautiful!</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object001_1.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment link="http://www.trussworks.com/trussworks/Blog/Entries/2012/5/26_Trussworks_Double_Deck_a_hit_at_Exhibitor_12.html#comment_layer" count="0" enabled="0"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trussworks partners with Stylmark on Interlock Products&#13;</title>
      <link>http://www.trussworks.com/trussworks/Blog/Entries/2011/9/6_Trussworks_partners_with_Stylmark_on_Interlock_Products.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f948aaa4-5051-4e01-9ee3-f640b5710632</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 6 Sep 2011 09:24:46 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>Trussworks &amp;amp; Stylmark are excited to announce a partnership that allows Trussworks to manufacture and market STOWaway and SNAPtruss truss systems to the exhibit industry. &lt;br/&gt;We feel that these 2 product lines are a great fit with our current offerings. STOWaway may look similar to EZ12 but the capabilities are much different. We are anxious to create kit offerings which will take advantage of STOWaway&#x2019;s strength. &lt;br/&gt;SNAPtruss has a loyal stocking distributor base which we are eager to serve. &lt;br/&gt;The lead times on these products in powder coated finish will soon match the other Trussworks products at 3-5 days!&lt;br/&gt;Click either link above to learn more about each of these fine products!</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object000.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment link="http://www.trussworks.com/trussworks/Blog/Entries/2011/9/6_Trussworks_partners_with_Stylmark_on_Interlock_Products.html#comment_layer" count="0" enabled="0"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>presenting the Astro workstation </title>
      <link>http://www.trussworks.com/trussworks/Blog/Entries/2010/5/5_presenting_the_Astro_workstation.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9304243-ec22-4ab9-a7e2-25404d8f4c36</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 5 May 2010 12:12:22 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>Dear Distributors,&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I hope you all had a solid spring season and are feeling optimistic about the future..&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Speaking of futuristic, (did I really just make that leap?) we were really infatuated with our MOD booth this year and very much felt the need to follow through on the concept we used to create it. Threading the Hyperlite verticals through a serpentine ladder truss has allowed us create a unique look with a recessed area on the front that is perfect for a monitor and keyboard shelf. The lower rear recessed area allows for a contoured CPU housing which nicely blends into the curvaceous design of the workstation. Graphics may be installed on &#xA0;just the front as shown in the rendering or on the front and back for use in island exhibits where it will be seen from all angles.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Astro without graphics retails for $2,415 including a case. 2 units will fit in one case.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;When used with front graphics and header only, graphics should retail for about $316. To apply graphics to the back as well, you would add $272 to that making the whole unit retail for $3,003.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As designed, the max monitor physical width is 23&amp;quot; but this dimension can easily be adjusted for minimal cost when ordering.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please give us your feedback on our new design!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thanks and happy selling!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Roy</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object000_1.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment link="http://www.trussworks.com/trussworks/Blog/Entries/2010/5/5_presenting_the_Astro_workstation.html#comment_layer" count="0" enabled="0"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOD 10</title>
      <link>http://www.trussworks.com/trussworks/Blog/Entries/2010/3/25_MOD_10.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a20158d-bd59-486a-b453-c37a8dda2fef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 13:50:51 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>MOD &#x2019;10 was a fantastic evening. It started out with a mini-tradeshow with great hors d'oeuvres and drinks  like last year. We tried something new with Hyperlite and it got a positive response so we will build on that style. &lt;br/&gt;After the tradeshow, we were treated to a fashion show with models wearing all kinds of outfits which were adorned with exhibit materials such  as LED lighting, Dazian fabrics and anodized aluminum pieces. Then the awards ceremony which was done in true Hollywood fashion with 4 judges but the voting was done by the audience. Next was dinner served buffet style and then many went on to enjoy the festivities at the Exhibit City News Party. We took apart our exhibit, carted it out of there and called it a night. It had been a long day..</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/MOD_10-Medium.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:badge type="movie"></iweb:badge>
      <iweb:comment link="http://www.trussworks.com/trussworks/Blog/Entries/2010/3/25_MOD_10.html#comment_layer" count="0" enabled="0"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exhibitor 2010</title>
      <link>http://www.trussworks.com/trussworks/Blog/Entries/2010/3/22_Exhibitor_%26_MOD_2010.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41342931-4077-4774-ab0c-a0f60bb76aa5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2010 17:41:57 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>Exhibitor 2010 - Building on the popular EZ612 Irvine / Hillcrest convex curve design, we extended the top curve forward into a ceiling supported by Hyperlite corner modules, we created an environment inside our booth which was somewhat insulated from the noise and lights of the show. It gave us a great place to demo our products and catch up with our distributors and old friends. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This was the first time we had used the curve in an island, doing graphics inside and out and it was a challenge. Optima rose to the challenge perfectly fitting the outside radius with a 19&#x2019;2&#x201D; wide x 10&#x2019;8&#x201D; high Trussworks banner. This was installed with our banner clips and every time I looked around the back of the booth, it had drawn an audience. Not bad for a static image. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Since we had most of our office staff at the show, we had to build in a small office. We did this out of Hyperlite and incorporated our overhead sign as well as a demo station on each side and placed PackStuff our front. While the office detracted from the design it proved to be quite useful and I don&#x2019;t think many people recognized it as an afterthought. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our front counter was also a hit with many of our distributors. It was simple but impactful as were our beautiful Iris and silver pack stools. Click on the booth above to check out the photo library. &lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/Exhibitor2010-Medium_3.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:badge type="movie"></iweb:badge>
      <iweb:comment link="http://www.trussworks.com/trussworks/Blog/Entries/2010/3/22_Exhibitor_%26_MOD_2010.html#comment_layer" count="0" enabled="0"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>sometimes you get what you pay for.. sometimes you don't!</title>
      <link>http://www.trussworks.com/trussworks/Blog/Entries/2010/1/21_sometimes_you_get_what_you_pay_for.._sometimes_you_dont%21.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6357d1a1-ebf4-4c81-bdea-b40f1dea4aba</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 13:28:36 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We get alot of calls asking us what the difference is between our EZ6 and a certain competitor's offering. We have also noticed some common &#xA0;misconceptions and I wanted to take a moment to play mythbuster..&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Myth: &#xA0;A competitor's truss is less expensive than our EZ6 truss.&lt;br/&gt;Fact: That is simply not true. As a matter of fact, on many identical kits, we beat their prices by as much as 20%. In a few cases, they are less, but we will price match.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Myth: A competitor's truss is also tool-less.&lt;br/&gt;Fact: If that were true, why would they sell the tool to loosen their twist lock? Fact is, those plastic connectors bind up under the tension making it too difficult to turn them by hand. EZ6 is the only true tool-less truss in this category.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Myth: If the manufacturer drew it, it'll work.&lt;br/&gt;Fact: Some truss does not have the structural integrity to successfully produce every kit some manufacturers design and promote. I have attached a photo depicting what happens when a truss system is used beyond it's capability. Note the lean.. the people in the foreground are standing straight. This kit looks great on paper and it would look great in EZ6 but if you want your verticals vertical and your graphics flat, you may want to steer clear of a product not designed for these stresses..&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In addition to the myths debunked above, EZ6 also has a lower piece count, a better graphic mounting system, more finishes, more accessories and component options and the ability to customize. If you are selling anything less than EZ6 in this category, please do your customers a favor and give us a call next time.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thanks and we look forward to hearing from you.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Roy&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object052.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment link="http://www.trussworks.com/trussworks/Blog/Entries/2010/1/21_sometimes_you_get_what_you_pay_for.._sometimes_you_dont%21.html#comment_layer" count="0" enabled="0"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>it's not just a Facade.. it's a light fixture!</title>
      <link>http://www.trussworks.com/trussworks/Blog/Entries/2009/11/18_its_not_just_a_Facade.._its_a_light_fixture%21.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb7f70ad-7de1-4244-b636-fed57d21151e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 13:18:52 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>Hi Everyone!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Man, it has been a brutal year but we're still here plugging away. We have been having some early success with our Hyperlite extrusion system due to the ease of assembly and felt like we can build on that simplicity by adding something totally new and unique. These new Hyperlite kits are the beginning of an entire new line of displays. Although you can't see the hardware, we are using the easy to assemble Hyperlite extrusions with the flat truss horizontals. But instead of showing that, we created 2 pc. laminated expanded PVC columns which mount to the extrusions. These columns also support and hide florescent strip lights which do a very nice job of lighting the large graphic panels or the built-in shelving. Optional column accessories include a perf metal sconce, small product shelves, monitor mounts and literature pockets. The horizontal trusses are still there to provide the structure to mount headers to and support the large fabric graphics. In keeping with all of our newer products, these kits are tool-less and pack in plastic shipping cases.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;So.. introducing the first 3 kits of the Hyperlite Facade line.&lt;br/&gt;The 10 x 10 Silhouette - retail as shown including graphics - $6,022&lt;br/&gt;The 10 x 20 Sabre - retail as shown including graphics - $15,350&lt;br/&gt;The 10 x 20 Navigator - retail as shown including graphics - $13,409&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We have put alot of energy into this new line are very excited about them and truly hope it will help you all increase your sales. Please feel free to contact us with questions on these or any of our other products.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Roy&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/Facades-Medium.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:badge type="movie"></iweb:badge>
      <iweb:comment link="http://www.trussworks.com/trussworks/Blog/Entries/2009/11/18_its_not_just_a_Facade.._its_a_light_fixture%21.html#comment_layer" count="0" enabled="0"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helios A/V uses Hyperlite behind the scenes</title>
      <link>http://www.trussworks.com/trussworks/Blog/Entries/2009/7/10_Helios_A_V_uses_Hyperlite_behind_the_scenes.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56ba61b0-5562-4ba6-ac0f-c0f68ea6fca3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 13:10:42 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>Dear Distributors,&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I believe you all have heard of our new Hyperlite system by now and I am sure you are tired of this long slow summer. I wanted to share with you all something that has helped keep us busy during the slow season which is not necessarily exhibit related although it demonstrates an alternative use for Hyperlite. Our good friends at Helios Interactive Technologies (&lt;a href="http://www.helios-av.com/"&gt;http://www.helios-av.com/&lt;/a&gt;) were commissioned to create some interactive storefront windows and needed to hang 3 large 200 pound SunCutter plasma screens next to each other and also perfectly align 8 Hi Definition projectors in each venue. The details were finalized a week before the first install in San Francisco.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We had previously worked with them on a few projects and they knew what we could do. Together we designed some specialty hardware including angled truss braces, a winch system to lift and hang the heavy monitors into place and graphic bars were used to keep the spacing perfect for the sensitive projectors. Due to the unique nature of each of the install locations, the final structure designs had to happen in the field and the flexibility of the Hyperlite system allowed them to work around uneven floors, obstacles and a myriad of other surprises to get all of their installs in SF and NY completed and operating within their deadline.&#xA0;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The requirements Helios had and the challenges they faced are very similar to what we deal with on a regular basis in our industry. Tight lead time, big heavy A/V equipment with high sensitivity to positioning and short installation times. Hyperlite helped make the hardware portion of the job easy.&#xA0;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;While Hyperlite does make beautiful tradeshow exhibits, &#xA0;(we now have some photos of exhibits in our gallery at &lt;a href="http://www.trussworks.com/Hyperlite_Photos.html)"&gt;http://www.trussworks.com/Hyperlite_Photos.html)&lt;/a&gt;, it can do so much more so keep it in mind the next time you need a very flexible yet strong structure.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Wishing you all a strong fall season!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Roy&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Roy Muller&lt;br/&gt;Trussworks</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/Helios_install-Medium.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:badge type="movie"></iweb:badge>
      <iweb:comment link="http://www.trussworks.com/trussworks/Blog/Entries/2009/7/10_Helios_A_V_uses_Hyperlite_behind_the_scenes.html#comment_layer" count="0" enabled="0"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <iweb:dateFormat>EEEE, MMMM d, yyyy</iweb:dateFormat>
    <iweb:baseURL>http://www.trussworks.com/trussworks/Blog</iweb:baseURL>
    <iweb:maximumSummaryItems>10</iweb:maximumSummaryItems>
  </channel>
</rss>
